

MYO MI MI SHARR

• DETAILS •

Singapore +6593714939 myomimisharr@gmail.com

> Date of birth 11 Aug 1991

Nationality Myanmar

LINKS

LinkedIn Profile

Portfolio Website

• SKILLS •

WordPress

PHP

HTML

CSS

Jquery

JavaScript

Bootstrap

SEO

React JS

MySQL

Adobe Photoshop

Figma

Git

SharePoint

Note JS

• LANGUAGES •

English

Myanmar

PROFILE

Hi, I'm Sharr, a web developer with more than 10 years of experience in developing web projects in fast-paced environments that require quick turnaround times. I graduated with a Bachelor of Engineering degree in Information Technology from Mandalay Technological University. I have hands-on experience using WordPress, PHP, HTML, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React.js, Photoshop, Figma, MySQL, Git, SEO, SFMC, Formsite, and SharePoint to create user-friendly websites.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering, Technological University, Mandalay

2011 - 2012

Graduated with high honors.

Bachelor of Technology, Technological University, Mandalay

2007 - 2011

Graduated with high honors.

Certificate of Completion WSQ Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) Training Course, Equinet Academy, Singapore

October 2022

Successfully completed Search Engine Optimization Course.

From Superpowers to Great Teams, IDEO UIDEO, Singapore

October 2023

Has completed the course requirements.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Developer at Ace Pointer Information Technology, Singapore

December 2021 — Present

- Planning website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with Wordpress, PHP, HTML, CSS, Jquery, JavaScript, API and other editing software.
- Overseeing back-end development using PHP to maintain website integrity, security and efficiency.
- Providing effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications.
- Following policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times.
- Implementing Google-based SEO and ad campaigns to meet budget specifications.

Web Developer at Agility Logistics, Singapore

December 2019 — November 2021

- Successfully identified, diagnosed, and fixed website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and formatting issues.
- Provided ongoing efficiency and security maintenance and patched on website interface to maintain viability after launch.
- Collaborated with Digital Marketing Team, representing web team to establish project goals, projections and milestones.

CMS Developer at Nexlabs Myanmar, Yangon

June 2017 — May 2019

- Focused PHP and HTML development outside of WordPress for landing pages, micro-sites, etc
- Coordinated with team of UX designers to create new Web Content Management system
- Maintained an organized workflow using a project management tool (like GitHub)

Web Essentials Lecturer at at Myanmar IT Consulting Training Center, Yangon

February 2016 — March 2019

- Lectured Web Essentials to graduated students from computer science universities and IT related fields
- Taught HTML, HTML5, CSS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Photoshop and WordPress in class on weekends only
- Led over 60 students per secession to comprehend their assignment
- Guided their web designing and web developing depend on their projects

CMS Developer at Revo Tech Myanmar, Yangon

October 2015 — May 2017

Web Developer & Web Designer at Apex Website & Software Services Co.,Ltd, Yangon $\tt July~2014-October~2015$

Web Developer & Web Designer at Myanmars.NET, Yangon

January 2013 — June 2014

★ MOST SUCCESSFUL TECHNOLOGICAL ACHIEVEMENT

Capitol Singapore, Restaurants & Cafes

Project Link

Chijmes, Food & Entertainment

Project Link

Agility, Asia Pacific Logistics

Project Link

Agility, All Insights

Project Link

Chindwin PSB, Private College

Project Link

Golden Hill Tower, Room Rental

Project Link